THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Death Penalty Research, 1968-2004; 5; 18
  - Hunter, Williams v. S. of South Carolina court transcripts, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
  - Hunter, William sentencing transcript South carolina *restricted*, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Idaho caselaw research, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Idaho coding sheets, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Illinois caselaw research, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Illinois Coding Sheets, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Index of Death Penalty Information from National Coaliton to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Indiana Caselaw research, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Indiana CJP Correspondence and funding, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Isaacs, Carl v. of Georgia Research Printouts, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Jackson, Carl v. of Flordia Research Photocopy, 1978 March 9 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jackson, Lucious v. Georgia- Brief for Petitioner, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Jackson, Ronald v. Florida Research Photocopy, 1978 October 26 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Jackson, Warren v. Louisiana Brief of Amicus Curiae, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Jackson v. Georgia Research Printout, 1975 April (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Jones, Louis v. United States 529 VS 848 Research Printout, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript, 1988 March 28 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida Court transcript vol. 1, 1991 March 11-13 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida Court transcript vol. 2, 1991 march 11-13 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida Court transcript vol. 3, 1991 March 11-13 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of florida court transcript vol. 4, 1991 march 11-13 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of florida court transcript vol. 5, 1988 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida Court transcript vol. 6, 1988 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of florida court transcript vol. 7, 1988 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of florida Court Transcript vol. 8, 1988 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida portion of court transcript (1 of 2), 1988 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jones, randall V. S. of Florida portion of court transcript (2 of 2), 1988 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jones, randall v. S. of florida research Printouts and notes, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Jones, randall Sentencing transcript Florida *restricted*, 1991 march 13 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jurek, Jerry V. texas/ Jurek V. estelle Research Photocopies, 1975; 1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Kentucky Caselaw Research, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Kentucky CJP correspondence, funding and Invoices, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lankford, Bryan V. Idaho Law week Photocopy, 1987 October 20; 1991 May 20 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lee, Rudolph V. S. of Florida research printout, 1974 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Legare V. s. of Georgia Correspondence and Petition for Cerfiorari, 1979 September 24 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lockett, Sandra V. S. of Ohio Research Printout, 1978 July 3 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Longworth, Richard v. S. Of South Carolina Court Transcipts, 1991 September 03 (Box 8, Folder 16-20)
  - Longworth Sentencing transcript (incomplete) *restricted*, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Lousiana Caselaw research, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Lousiana CJP correspondence and funding, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Lyons, Robbie v. S. of North Carolina brief of appellant, 2002 July 30 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lyons, Robbie v. S. of North Carolina motion for Appropriate relief, 1997 April 14 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lyons, Robbie v. S. of North carolina transcript of the sentencing phase vol. 3 (1 of 2), 1994 April 25 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lyons, robbie v. S. of north carolina transcript Of the sentencing phase vol. 3 (2 of 2), 1994 April 15 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kentucky caselaw research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Mann, larry v. Richard dugger appeal from the U.s. district court for middle district of Florida, 1987 May 04 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Marlowe, Gordon V. S. of North carolina court transcript, 1989 November 09 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Marlowe, Gordon V. S. of North carolina court transcript, 1989 November 09 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Martin, Nollie V. Louie wainwright research Printout, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Maryland caselaw research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Maryland CJP Correspondence, 1996 November 16 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Massachussetts 411 NE 2nd 1274 research Photocopy, 1980 October 28 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Massachussetts Campaign Against Restoration of the Death Penalty Reprint of Sufolk County DA V. Watson Decision, 1981 October 28 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Death Penalty Hearings, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Franklin/Hampshire/hampden conference, 1991 March 02 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - McClesky, Warren v. Ralph Kemp on Writ of Certiorari, 1987 April 22 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - McCleskey, Warren v. Walter Zant affidavit of William J. Bowers, 1980 December 30 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - McCleskey V. Zant Law Week printout, 1991 April 16 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Mcrae, James v. S. of Florida Motion for Rehearing, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - McCree, Ardia v. A. L. Lockhart Reseach Printout, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Mckoy, Douk v. North Carolina Law Week Printout, 1990 March 06 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Menendez, Antonio v. of Florida research Printout, 1979 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Mitchell, William v. Joe Hopper Research Printouts, 1982 April 01 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Middleton, Frank Jr. v. of South Carolina Court Transcript, 1987 September 21-28 (Box 9, Folder 24-26)
  - Middleton, Frank Jr. v. of South Carolina Research Notes and Printouts, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Middleton, Frank Sentencing Transcript South Carolina *restricted*, Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Mikenas, Mark v. of Florida Research Printout, 1979 March 07 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - "Mills v. Maryland: The supereme court guarantees the consideration of mitigation circumstances pursuant to Lockett V. Ohio", Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Minute Order Form, Northern District Illinois, 1986 October (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Mississippi caselaw research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Missouri caselaw research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Missouri CJP correspondence and funding, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Montana Caselaw research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Moore, William V. Charles Balkcom Brief for Appellee- Cross Appellant, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Moore V. S. of Georgia Research Photocopy, 1975 January (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Moore, William V. S. of Georgia Trial Report and Research Printout, Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Morgan, Derrick v. of Illinois Law Week Printout, 1979 June 16 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Morgan, Derrick v. Illinois On writ of Certiorari Reply Brief, 1991 October (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Morgan v. of Georgia Reseach Photocopy, 1974 September (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Mu'min, Dawud v. Virginia On Writ of Certiorari, 1991 May 30 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Murray, Edward, Director, Virginia Dept. of Corrections v. Giarratano, Watkins, Boggs et al., 1989 June 23 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Nebraska Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - New Hampshire Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - New Hampshire CJP Correspondence, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - New Hampshire Superior Court Order Addressing Capital Murder Statute, 1991 January (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - New Jersey Case Law Research, 1989 July 25 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - New Jersey CJP Correspondence, 1994; 1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - New Mexico Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - New York CJP Correspondence and Research, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Nevada Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - North Carolina CJP Correspondence Regarding Funding, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - North Carolina Research Printout, 1983 November (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Ohio CJP Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Oklahoma Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - O'Neal, Robert v. Commonwealth of Massachusetts Transcripts and Printouts, 1975 April - December (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Oregon Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Oregon CJP Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Patton v. Mississippi Certiorari to the Supreme Court of Mississippi, 1947 December 8 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Payne, Peruis v. Tennessee Law Week Printout, 1991 June 25 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania CJP Correspondence and Funding, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Correspondence and Survey Instruments, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Penry, Johnny v. James Lynaugh Research Printout from Supreme Court Reporter, 1989 June 26 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The People v. Mateo 811 NE 2nd 1053 Research Printout, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 1, 1989 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 2, 1988 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 3, 1988 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 4, 1988 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 5, 1988 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 6, 1988 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Circuit Court Transcript Vol. 7, 1988 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony V. S. of Florida Sentencing and Motion for New Trial, 1988 October 7 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Ponticelli, Anthony v. of Florida Research Notes and Printouts, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Powell V. Alabama Research Photocopy, 1932 November 7 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Proffitt, Charles v. Lowie Wainwright Research Photocopy, 1982 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "The Psychology of Telling Murder Stories: Do We Think in 2002 Scripts, Exemplar; or Prototypes?" by R.L. Wiener, T.L. Richmond (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Pullin v. of Georgia Research Photocopy, 1976 September (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 1, 1989 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 2, 1989 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 3, 1989 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 4, 1989 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 5, 1989 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 6, 1989 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 7, 1989 June 5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 8, 1989 June 5 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Randolph, Richard v. Of Florida Research Printouts from Websites, 2001 November 7 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Randolph, Richard Sentencing Transcript Florida *restricted*, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Transcript of Proceedings, 1989 March 7 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Randolph, Richard v. of Florida Transcript of Sentencing, 1989 April 5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Research Photocopies on D. P. Cases from Published Sources, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Research Printouts and Notes on Death Penalty with Remarks from Jon Sorensen, 1983-2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Research Printout "The Strange Case of Howard Pearle", 2003 February 11 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Research Prinout the United States Law Week 53 LW 3773, 1985 April 30 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Rocheville, David v. of South Carolina Court Transcripts, 1991 July 8-15 (Box 11, Folder 11-15)
  - Rocheville, David v. of South Carolina Research Printouts and Motes, 2000-2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Rocheville, David Sentencing Transcript *restrcited*, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Saffle, James V. Robyn Parks On writ of Certiorari Law Week Printout, 1990 March 6 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Salvatore, Michael v. of Florida Research Photocopy, 1979 February 14 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Sawyer, Anthony v. of Florida Research Printout, 1975 February 13 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Schad, Edward v. Arizona On writ of Certiorari, 1991 June 18 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Schmeck v. of California Death Penalty Transcript on Appeal Vol. 2, 1989 May 8-9 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerks Transcript on Appeal Vol. 3, 1989 May 8-9 (Box 11, Folder 23-25)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerk's Transcript on Appeal Vol. 4, 1989 November 6 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerk's Transcript on Appeal Vol. 4, 1989 November 6 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerk's Transcript on Appeal Vol. 5 (1 of 2), 1989 December 21 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerk's Transcript on Appeal Vol. 6, 1989 May 17-18 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Daily Transcript Vol. 7, 1989 May 22-23 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Penalty Transcript on Appeal Vol. 8, 1989 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Penalty Transcript on Appeal Vol. 9, 1989 June 6-7 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 10, 1989 June 12 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 11, 1989 June 13-14 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 12, 1989 June 19-20 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 13, 1989 June 21-22 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 14, 1989 June 26-27 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 15, 1989 June 28-29 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 16, 1989 July 5-6 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 17, 1989 July 10 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 18, 1989 July 11 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 19, 1989 July 12-13 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 20, 1989 July 17 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 21, 1989 July 18 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 22, 1989 July 19-20 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 23, 1989 July 24 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 24, 1989 July 25 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 25, 1989 July 26 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 26, 1989 July 27 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 28, 1989 August 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 29, 1989 September 5-6 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 30, 1989 September 11 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 31, 1989 September 12 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 32, 1989 September 13-14 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 33, 1989 September 18 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 34, 1989 September 19 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 35, 1989 September 20 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 36, 1989 September 21 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 37, 1989 September 25 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 38, 1989 September 26 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 39, 1989 September 27-28 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 40, 1989 October 2-3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 41, 1989 October 4-5 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 42, 1989 October 10-11 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 43, 1989 October 16-17 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Schmeck, Mark v.of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 44, 1989 October 24-25 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 45, 1989 October 26 - November 06 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 46, 1989 November 07-16 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 47, 1989 November 21-27 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 48, 1989 November 28 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 49, 1989 November 30 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 51, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 52, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 53, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 54, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Death Transcript on Appeal Vol. 56, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerk's Trasncript on Appeal Vol. 1, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerks Transcripts on Appeal (1 of 2) Vol. 2, 1990 April 05 (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerks Transcript Vol. 3, 1990 April 05 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerks Transcript on Appeal vol. 4, 1990 April 05 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Clerks Transcript on Appeal Vol. 5, 1990 April 05 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California General Index and Proceedings of May 2, 1989, 1989 May 02 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Portions of Court Transcripts, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Preliminary Examination Transcript Vol. 1, 1987 February 26 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Preliminary Examination Transcript Vol. 2, 1987 February- March (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Reporter's Transcript Master Index, 1986 July 17 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Removed Transcript Volume Covers with Volume Page Ranges, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Requests and Motions (Assorted), 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Reporters Transcript on Appeal Cover Pages, 1989 May- December (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Reporter's Transcript on Appeal Master Index, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California Reporters's Transcript corrected pages, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
  - Schmeck Sentencing Transcript *restricted*, 1989 December 21 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Schmeck, Mark v. of California unsorted Portion of Transcript, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Shepherd et al. v. Florida Opinion of the Court, 1950 October (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Shae, William v. of Florida Research Photocopy, 1978 December 07 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Simmons, Jonathan v. of South Carolina, 1992 December 02 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Simmons, Jonathan v. South Carolina on Writ of Certiorari and Research Photocopy, 1994 June 17 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Dennis v. of Florida Research Photocopy, 1978 November 09 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Jimmy v. Louise Wainwright Appeal from the U.S. Distrcit Court for the Northern District of Florida, 1985 November 14 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Smith, John v. Charles Balkcom petition for Writ of Certiorari, 1981 October (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Smith, John v. Charles Balkcom Petitioner Smith's Appendices, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Smith, John v. Balkcom Research Printout, 1982 March 29 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Kenneth v. of Texas Statement of Facts and Closing Arguments, 1990 June 15 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Spinkellink, John v. Louie Wainwright Order Regarding Writ of Habeas Corpus, 1977 September 23 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Spinkellink, John v. Wainwirght Federal Petition, Correspndence from Law Firm, and Federal Reporter Photocpy, 1979 March 05 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Squires, William v. of Florida Motion to Vacate Judgment, 1990 May 28 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - South Carolina Folder Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - South Carolina Folder CJP Correspondence and Funding, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - South Dakota folder Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee Caselaw Research, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee Folder CJP Correspondence and Funding, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Texas Caselaw Research, Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Torrence, Thomas v. of South Carolina Court Transcripts Vol. 1, 1992 May 18-25 (Box 16, Folder 20-22)
  - Torrence, Thomas v. of South Carolina Court Transcript Vol. 2, 1992 May 18-25 (Box 16, Folder 23-25)
  - Torrence, Thomas v. of South Carolina Court Transcript Vol. 3, 1992 May 18-25 (Box 16, Folder 26-27)
  - Torrence, Thomas v. of South Carolina Court Transcript Vol. 3, 1992 May 18-25 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Torrence, Thomas v. of South Carolina Court Transcript Vol. 4, 1992 May 18-25 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - Torrence, Thomas v. of South Carolina Research Printouts and Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Torrence, John Sentencing Transcript *restricted*, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 1, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 2, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 3, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 4, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 5, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 6, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 7, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 8, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 9, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 21, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 22, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 23, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 24, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Trepal, George v. of Florida Court Transcript Vol. 25, 1991 January-Febraury (Box 17, Folder 20)